My name is Isaiah James. I'm an Iraq war veteran. I went two times to Iraq. Also went once to
Afghanistan. My job in the Army was 11 Bravo. For those who don't know, that's infantry.
My additional skill identifier is Bravo 4. For those who don't know, that is a sniper.
First deployment was 15 months. Second deployment was 12 months. Third deployment was 12 months.
So I've been there. 39 months of combat. Straight fighting. I could take a rifle and clear a room
and do all this crazy stuff. I've air assaulted out of helicopters. I've grabbed dudes and put bags
over their heads and zip tied them and put them on helicopters and saw them being flown away and
they've never seen again. The Iraq war did not need to happen. It should not have happened. Iraq did
nothing to us and we killed a million Iraqi civilians, lost 5,000 plus American soldiers. For what? It
diminished our standing in the world. It damn near bankrupted our coffers. All it did was make the
war machine get bigger and stronger in America. I think anybody who's been shot at and blown up
and seen people blown to literal pieces is anti-war. If you're not, and this is for, I'm speaking
directly to every veteran out there. If you love war, then you've never actually been in it.
If you, I don't give a damn if you serve, then you've never seen somebody take their last breath
in a violent situation. You've never seen it. I have. It's not pretty.